<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://ukhamitov.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://ukhamitov.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-02-18T08:08:45+00:00</updated><id>https://ukhamitov.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ᴜʀᴀʟ ᴋʜᴀᴍɪᴛᴏᴠ</title><subtitle>Personal blog</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Game lists</title><link href="https://ukhamitov.com/game-management" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Game lists" /><published>2021-04-15T16:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-04-15T16:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://ukhamitov.com/game-management</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ukhamitov.com/game-management">&lt;p&gt;Recently I prefer to play video games. When I was a kid I missed a lot of games that were hit. I like different games in different genres, but after а while, I forget about what was the game, liked or not. When friends ask me what I played recently I just don’t remember.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I researched a few sites and applications for managing lists of the completed games, but they all had a lot of features that I don’t need. I almost started writing my own application, but then it dawned on me. Completing a specific game is a “task”. These tasks have a single goal - to complete the games this year. What tool helps with the organization of goals and objectives? Chaos Control, of course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I built a structure of lists and I want to share what I get as a result:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ukhamitov.com/public/images/games_lists/all_lists.png&quot; alt=&quot;Chaos-Control&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When a game is announced I place it on the “waiting list”. I add to this list the games that have been announced because if I didn’t do it I’ll forget to play them later :) The task’s start date is responsible for the release date of the game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ukhamitov.com/public/images/games_lists/waiting_list.png&quot; alt=&quot;Chaos-Control&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the game from the Waiting list is released I add it to the Backlog list. This is a list of games I want to play. (I hope I’ll have enough time for that, LOL).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ukhamitov.com/public/images/games_lists/backlog.png&quot; alt=&quot;Chaos-Control&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I start playing, I transfer the game from the Backlog to the list of the current year. If I started playing the game in one year and complete it the next year, then the tasks are accordingly moved to another list. The task completion date is set after completing the game. Completed games are marked with a checkmark. Also, I write a little note about the game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I created the Games 2001-2016 list, which includes a dozen and a half years. I did it because many completed games have already been forgotten. In this list, I’ve included the games I played on PC, PS Vita, 3DS, and Wii U.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Games 2017-2020. These lists are merged by years. It’s hard to fill that list because I don’t remember what I played :) For example, here is a list of this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ukhamitov.com/public/images/games_lists/games_2021.png&quot; alt=&quot;Chaos-Control&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dropped. Games that I stopped to play for some reason. Actually, this list has a one-game - Journey. I don’t know why, but this game so boring, sorry fans :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ukhamitov.com/public/images/games_lists/games_dropped.png&quot; alt=&quot;Chaos-Control&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Ural Khamitov</name></author><category term="games" /><summary type="html">Recently I prefer to play video games. When I was a kid I missed a lot of games that were hit. I like different games in different genres, but after а while, I forget about what was the game, liked or not. When friends ask me what I played recently I just don’t remember.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hello world</title><link href="https://ukhamitov.com/hello-world" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello world" /><published>2020-11-11T15:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-11-11T15:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://ukhamitov.com/hello-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ukhamitov.com/hello-world">&lt;p&gt;Hi there! This is my first post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Ural Khamitov and I’m an Android developer currently working for &lt;a href=&quot;https://chaos-control.mobi/&quot;&gt;Chaos Control&lt;/a&gt;. I decide to write some little posts about everything, but in English. It’s helpful to practice my English skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tunned!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Ural Khamitov</name></author><category term="lifestyle" /><summary type="html">Hi there! This is my first post.</summary></entry></feed>